export const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "17 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
        options: ["10", "20", "17"],
        correct: "10",
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "45 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
        options: ["50", "45", "40"],
        correct: "50",
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "75 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
        options: ["70", "80", "175"],
        correct: "80",
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "19 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
        options: ["20", "10", "19"],
        correct: "20",
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "64 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
        options: ["64", "70", "60"],
        correct: "70",
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "0 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
        options: ["10", "1", "0"],
        correct: "0",
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "98 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
        options: ["80", "100", "89"],
        correct: "100",
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "199 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
        options: ["190", "100", "200"],
        correct: "200",
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "94 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
        options: ["100", "94", "90"],
        correct: "100",
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "165 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
        options: ["160", "170", "150"],
        correct: "170",
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: "445 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
        options: ["450", "440", "500"],
        correct: "450",
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: "999 rounded off to the nearest 10 is...",
        options: ["990", "1000", "909"],
        correct: "990",
    },
];